<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Application and User Data on Azure Storage</title>
    <link>https://azurestorage.com/docs/application-and-user-data/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Application and User Data on Azure Storage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://azurestorage.com/docs/application-and-user-data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Azure Blob Storage data protection features</title>
      <link>https://azurestorage.com/docs/application-and-user-data/basics/azure-blob-storage-data-protection-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azurestorage.com/docs/application-and-user-data/basics/azure-blob-storage-data-protection-features/</guid>
      <description>Azure Blob Storage data protection features #   Enterprises, partners, and IT professionals store business-critical data in Azure Blob Storage. We are committed to providing the best-in-class data protection and recovery capabilities to keep your applications running. In this video, learn more about the Azure Blob Storage data protection features.
 Learn more about Data Protection &amp;amp; Security Azure Defender for Storage Immutable Blob storage  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Blob Storage Upload API&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://azurestorage.com/docs/application-and-user-data/basics/azure-blob-storage-upload-apis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azurestorage.com/docs/application-and-user-data/basics/azure-blob-storage-upload-apis/</guid>
      <description>Azure Blob Storage Upload API&amp;rsquo;s #  Customers typically use existing applications such as AzCopy, Azure Storage Explorer, etc. or the Azure Storage SDK&amp;rsquo;s when building custom apps to access the Azure Storage API&amp;rsquo;s. However, a good understanding of the API&amp;rsquo;s is critical when tuning your uploads for high performance. This document provides an overview of the different upload API&amp;rsquo;s to help you compare the differences between them.
 NOTE: There are some nuances with how the APIs are used based on what version of the API you are using.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFS 3.0 support for Azure Blob Storage</title>
      <link>https://azurestorage.com/docs/application-and-user-data/basics/nfs-3-support-for-azure-blob-storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azurestorage.com/docs/application-and-user-data/basics/nfs-3-support-for-azure-blob-storage/</guid>
      <description>NFS 3.0 support for Azure Blob Storage #   In this video, we introduce Azure Blob NFS 3.0 support, the only public cloud object storage offering native file system compatibility. Learn about NFS support and how to accelerate your workload migration from on premise datacenters to Azure.
 Learn more Step by step guide Contact us: BlobNFSFeedback@microsoft.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimize your costs with Azure Blob Storage</title>
      <link>https://azurestorage.com/docs/application-and-user-data/basics/optimize-your-costs-with-azure-blob-storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azurestorage.com/docs/application-and-user-data/basics/optimize-your-costs-with-azure-blob-storage/</guid>
      <description>Optimize your costs with Azure Blob Storage #   In this video, learn about the Azure Blob Storage features that help you save cost and keep your Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) low.
 Learn more about Azure Storage redundancy Tiers and lifecycle Reservations Network routing preference  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
